Martin Bogado

Frontend Developer

Contact

- Buenos Aires, Argentina
- in /in/martinbogado
- github.com/martinbogado
- 🔀 martinbogado@live.com.ar
- Portfolio website

Skills

- Js JavaScript
- React
- N Next.js
- 💪 Redux
- TS Typescript
- Sass
- Material UI
- (B) Node.js
- **S** Sanity.io
- Solidity
- Figma

Languages

- English B2 Upper Intermediate

 First Certificate in English
- Spanish Native

Volunteer Experience

ETHxperience

Aug 2022

Participation as a volunteer in the largest side event in the ETHLatam 2022. Help in the content creation for twitter

About

Passionate about technology, science and innovation. I have a background in the biotechnology's field, now I am dabbling to the IT world, I trained as a Full Stack Developer and I am strongly oriented to Frontend, Web3 development and UI design. I am the type of person who seizes every opportunity to learn something new.

Projects - Academic Experience

Llamas Finance 🏆 Hackathon Winning Project

Frontend Developer | Chainlink Spring 2022 Hackathon | May 2022

Participation in an agile development team where I worked on the design and the frontend of this project. We wanted to fix the broken annuity industry by proving how smart contracts are the solution to fixed annuities. A fixed annuity is a contract between you and an insurance provider. It can act as a safe place for cash to accumulate interest tax deferred. You pay a lump sum of income, and in exchange, the insurance provider guarantees your principal plus a minimum interest rate fixed over a multi-year time horizon.

Celominder

Full Stack Developer | Platzi's CELO Solidity Dev Program | June 2022

HabitTracker created for Platzi's CELO Solidity Dev Program. The idea is to generate an own economic incentive so that the user is more motivated to acquire new habits.

Experience



SoyHabitue

Frontend Developer | June 2022 - Present

Habitué is a startup that helps you digitize your business to sell online, without commissions. I work as a Frontend developer in the development of a fully functional Dashboard for business management, branches and customer orders.



SoyHenry

Full-Stack Teaching Assistant | Sep 2021 - Nov 2021

Bootcamp Assistant (TA) for Full-Stack Development Students

- Coordinate a group of students to achieve integration.
- · Guide students in the first steps of the course
- Assist to solve exercises and promote group collaboration
- Propose ideas to improve the Bootcamp processes

Education

CELO Solidity Dev Program Student

Platzi Scholarship | May 2022 - June 2022

In this program we learn from experts and referents about how to advance and build a development project through an EVM blockchain like CELO.

Full Stack Web Developer

HENRY Bootcamp | Aug 2021 - Nov 2021

+ 800hs of full-time training in current web development technologies, dynamics of Pair Programming and soft skills boost